Imagine having to win over the girl of your dreams... every friggin' day.
50 First Dates is a comedy, romance film directed by Peter Segal.
Henry is a player skilled at seducing women.
But when this veterinarian meets Lucy, a girl with a quirky problem when it comes to total
recall, he realizes it's possible to fall in love all over again…and again, and again.
That's because the delightful Lucy has no short-term memory, so Henry must woo
her day after day until he finally sweeps her off her feet.
Henry Roth, played by Adam Sandler.
Lucy Whitmore, played by Drew Barrymore.
Ula, played by Rob Schneider.
Doug Whitmore, played by Sean Astin.
Alexa, played by Lusia Strus.
Dr. Keats, played by Dan Aykroyd.
50 First Dates is a 2004 American romantic comedy film directed by Peter Segal and starring Adam Sandler and Drew
Barrymore, with Rob Schneider, Sean Astin, Lusia Strus, Blake Clark, and Dan Aykroyd in supporting roles.
It follows the story of Henry Roth, a womanizing marine veterinarian
who falls for an art teacher named Lucy Whitmore.
When he discovers she has amnesia, and forgets him when she falls
asleep, he resolves to win her over again each new day.
Most of the film was shot on location in Oahu, Hawaii, on
the Windward side and the North Shore.
Sandler and Barrymore won an MTV Movie Award for Best On-Screen Team.
The film received mixed reviews but was a commercial success.
It was later remade in India as Satyabhama (2007, in Telugu) and as Ormayundo Ee Mukham (2014, in Malayalam), in Japan as
50 First Kisses (2018), in Iran as Chap dast (2005), and in Mexico as Como si fuera la primera vez (2019).
The film marked the second collaboration between Sandler and Barrymore, after The
Wedding Singer and before Blended (both directed by Frank Coraci).
During the end credits, it featured a dedication to the memory of Sandler's father
Stanley, who had died at the age of 68 from lung cancer on September 9, 2003.
The film explores themes of amnesia, hawaii, romcom, deception, womanizer.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.